{
    "subject": "resource/Ray_Brassier",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Nick_Land",
    "human_readable": "Ray Brassier was influenced by Nick Land.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.981440007686615,
            "question": "Was Nick Land a source of inspiration for Ray Brassier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9501691460609436,
            "question": "How has Nick Land's influence shaped Ray Brassier's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9073054790496826,
            "question": "Who influenced Ray Brassier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8281817436218262,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ray Brassier and Nick Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652674317359924,
            "question": "What philosophical connections can be made between Ray Brassier and Nick Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089926600456238,
            "question": "What are some potential areas of overlap in the philosophies of Ray Brassier and Nick Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696961522102356,
            "question": "Name a thinker who had an impact on Ray Brassier's work."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6686913967132568,
            "question": "Can you identify any shared ideas or concepts between Ray Brassier's work and Nick Land's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23886455595493317,
            "question": "Who are some key figures in the intellectual background of Ray Brassier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1985093504190445,
            "question": "Based on their relationship, what can we infer about Ray Brassier's intellectual interests?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ray Brassier was influenced by Nick Land.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some key figures in the intellectual background of Ray Brassier?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify any shared ideas or concepts between Ray Brassier's work and Nick Land's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a thinker who had an impact on Ray Brassier's work.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3898_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Ray Brassier is an editor of the collection Fanged Noumena, which includes works by Nick Land. Furthermore, the texts mention that Land's work has continued to exert influence, both through philosophers like Ray Brassier and other cultural producers. Therefore, it can be inferred that Ray Brassier was influenced by Nick Land\u2019s philosophical ideas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}